# **Christophe Domingos, Ph.D.**

**J** +351 912172797 christophedomingos@campus.ul.pt

G

#### **Personal Statement**

Dedicated to exploring human behavior and researching mental health. I'm a pioneer in EEG and sports research in Portugal, with extensive experience in EEG recording and data analysis. Working abroad and collaborating with international peers has resulted in impactful publications. I was honored with a prestigious sports medicine award and scholarships. As the Principal Investigator on a neuroscience project, I honed my leadership and research skills.

### **Professional Experience**

02/2023 - 09/2023		<b>Assistant Professor</b> , Institute of Psychology - Jagiellonian University, Kraków, Poland
		Uncovered insights into schizophrenia using EEG and fMRI.

10/2021 - 01/2023		<b>Postdoctoral Researcher</b> , Life Quality Research Centre – ESDRM, Rio Maior, Portugal
		As Principal Investigator, pioneered brain mapping during exercise via wireless EEG.

# **Academic Qualifications**

10/2015 - 01/2020		Ph.D. in Exercise Physiology, Faculty of Human Kinetics, Lisbon, Portugal
		EEG Neurofeedback in Active and Athlete Students: A Methodological Approach

09/2013 - 07/2015 M.Sc. in Exercise and Health, Faculty of Human Kinetics, Lisbon, Portugal

09/2010 - 07/2013 **B.Sc.** in Sports Science, University of Évora, Évora, Portugal

#### **Skills** Beginner **Proficient** Intermediate

Languages Portuguese English French

**Programming** Matlab Java Script Python

Data Analysis SPSS R Tableau

Data Management SQL Excel SnowFlake

Academic Research

## **Academic Accomplishments**

Miscellaneous

H-Index **Publications Projects** Awards **12** 

Writing & Editing

**Publishing** 

Consultation

**IATEX**